<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MTC</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="app">MTC</string>


    <string name="map_api_key">AIzaSyDI3q3wXZopQVS1HVyvFhfmGOuHdCPEcX8</string>


    <string name="amme_brief">
        The AMME is regularly scheduled. The conference offers scientific sessions,\n
        separate exhibition and seminars that will be devoted to the presentation  \n
        of latest achievements in mechanical applications
    </string>

    <string name="iceeing_brief">
        The ICEENG is regularly scheduled. The conference offers scientific sessions,\n
        separate exhibition and seminars that will be devoted to the presentation \n
        of latest achievements in electrical applications
    </string>

    <string name="icccae_brief">
        The ICCAE is regularly scheduled. The conference offers scientific sessions,\n
        separate exhibition and seminars that will be devoted to the presentation \n
        of latest achievements in civil and architecture engineering applications
    </string>

    <string name="icee_brief">
The ICEE is regularly scheduled. The conference offers scientific sessions,\n
        separate exhibition and seminars that will be devoted to the presentation \n
        of latest achievements in chemical and environmental engineering applications
    </string>

    <string name="icmep_brief">
The ICMEP is regularly scheduled. The conference offers scientific sessions,\n
        separate exhibition and seminars that will be devoted to the presentation \n
        of latest achievements in Mathematics and Engineering Physics applications.
    </string>

    <string name="asat_brief">
The ASAT is held every two years. The conference is accompanied by international \n
        exhibition where local and international companies present their products \n
        in the field of aerospace sciences and aviation technologies
    </string>
    <string name="mtc_hist_1">Prior to 1958, Egypt had long been without technological military educational facilities.
        Therefore, the Military Technical College (MTC) was established to aid fulfilling one the basic principles of the
        23rd of July revolution; “to build a strong Egyptian army“. As a milestone in building this army, the role of recent
        technologies and modern trends in armament came to mind. Thus, the idea of establishing a technical military academy
        became essential to supply the newborn army with engineers who constitute its technical mind.</string>
    <string name="obj">MTC is considered one of the distinguished scientific research centers of the Armed Forces.
        MTC is specialized in the fields of military sciences and technology. As a reference in the military technical applications .</string>
    <string name="mostafa">Maj. Gen. Dr. :\n Mostafa Mohamed Abdel Wahab \n Commandant of MTC</string>
    <string name="seleim">Lt. General :\ Mohamed Ibrahim Hassan Selim \n Founder of MTC </string>
    <string name="conf_1">The Military Technical College, Cairo, Egypt, has the pleasure to organize the third international undergraduate research conference
        (IUGRC-2018) in July 30 - Aug 2, 2018, Cairo, Egypt.</string>
    <string name="conf_2">The IUGRC aims to provide undergraduate engineering students from various specializations/majors with the opportunity
        to present their research work on the latest engineering applications. Students at all levels of undergraduate are invited to participate
        to gain hands on experience. Evaluations will be based on the originality of the work presented, the quality of the
        analytical and experimental work as well as the level of technical presentation.</string>


</resources>
